<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="info">info</string>
    <string name="edit_auto_login">Edit Auto login options</string>
    <string name="placeholder_username">username</string>
    <string name="placeholder_password">password</string>
    <string name="set_username">"username: "</string>
    <string name="set_password">"Password: "</string>
    <string name="save_autologin">save</string>
    <string name="enable_autologin_preference">Enable Autologin:</string>
    <string name="DScribeInfoTitle">D.Scribe Settings</string>
    <string name="DScribeInfo">Scribe is a social link aggregation and discussion platform, powered by Lemmy. Content is organized into communities, so it is easy to subscribe to topics that you are interested in, and ignore others.</string>
    <string name="DScribeDialog">To continue you need to install Voyager first.\\nPlease select install to continue with the installation on F-Droid.</string>
    <string name="action_audio">Mumble</string>
    <string name="AudioTitle">Audio Info</string>
    <string name="AudioInfo">Disroot\'s Audio is powered by Mumble. Mumble is a free, open source, low latency, high quality voice chat application. It was originally intended for gamers, but it can be use to organize audio meeting, conference, etc.</string>
    <string name="AudioDialog">To continue you need to install Mumla first.\\nPlease select install to continue with the installation on F-Droid</string>
    <string name="AkkomaTitle">Akkoma Info</string>
    <string name="AkkomaInfo">Akkoma is a microblogging server software that can federate (= exchange messages with) other servers that support ActivityPub, like Friendica, GNU Social, Hubzilla, Mastodon, Misskey, Peertube, and Pixelfed.</string>
    <string name="AkkomaDialog">To continue you need to install Fedilab first.\\nPlease select install to continue with the installation on F-Droid</string>
    <string name="LibreTranslateTitle">Translate Info</string>
    <string name="LibreTranslateInfo">Disroot\'s Translate is a machine translation service, powered by LibreTranslate. LibreTranslate supports a lot of languages. It is an useful tool for those wishing to translate text between different languages. It is also a valuable tool for developers wishing to create translation applications.</string>
</resources>